Hi!
For my final trick shot.
This is probably the most impressive one that I've got.
What I got here is I've got the one ball and the 9 ball holding up the 8 ball.
How did I do that?
Take your hand, hold the 2 balls against the rail, just kind of hammer them down a little bit, rest the 8 ball on top of them, and let go.
Now, the object of this shot is I'm going to hit the 8 ball with the cue ball without hitting the 1 or the 9.
It takes a lot of strength, it takes a lot of agility and for the person standing here, it takes a lot of guts.
Alright Jeff, I want you to come here and stand right where I'm standing.
The reason I'm having Jeff stand here is because I messed this shot up once.
When I did the cue ball went flying off the table and it broke a mirror.
I really got in trouble with the management.
Jeff's going to stand there and be ready to catch the ball or absorb it into his abs in case anything were to go wrong.
Now, I'm going to go to the other side of the table and we're going to have the shot.
Alright, so here I am.
I'm ready to do the trick shot now.
I got the cue ball all set up, the 8 ball is still stacked on the 1 and 9, and my buddy Jeff is making sure that the cue ball won't break anything important.
Lining it up.
With all my mite.
Hit the 8 ball first.
How did I do it?
Pretty simple.
You don't hit the ball really hard, you don't break a mirror, but when you hit the cue ball, just make sure it's going to go towards the 8 and half way there, give the table a little bump.
The 8 ball will fall down, cue ball hits the 8 ball, everyone laughs, buys you drinks, and the mayor will hand you the key to the city.